Beschrijving van de collection Cornelis Hendrik van Schooneveld
Universiteitsbibliotheek Leiden
- Archives regarding Mouton and related activities (inv. nos. 1-13)., A.
  - Mouton editor's correspondence., 1.; Correspondence, in alphabetical order by name, concerning manuscripts that were earmarked for publication in the Mouton series Slavistic printings and reprintings, Janua linguarum and De proprietatibus litterarum.; 97 boxes.; Every manuscript (in some case th
    - N
      2572. N’Diaye, G. - 2573. Nababan, S. - 2574. Nababan, W. - 2575. Nagy, G.O. - 2576. Naik, M. - 2577. Naish, C.M. - 2578. Nakeeb, D.G. - 2579. Nakeeb, D.G. (The earliest Dostoevsky). - 2580. Nalimov, V.V. (Probabilistic model of language). - 2581. Nardroff, E. von - 2582. Nash, R. - 2583. Nasjleti, D. (The Spanish preterite: its aspectual features in a standard dialect). - 2584. Nasr, Raja T. - 2585. Naumann, M.T. (Nabokov’s short stories). - 2586. Naylor, K.E. (The nominal declension in the Čakavian Serbocroation dialects and literary...). - 2587. Nebel, H.M. - 2588. Nedjalkov, V.P. - 2589. Nekimken, A.L. (The impact of Bertolt Brecht on society and the development of political theatre in Turkey). - 2590. Nelson, P.B. - 2591. Nelson, P.K. (The functions of figures of speech in selected anti-realistic novels). - 2592. Nelson, T.A. - 2593. Nemoianu, V.P. (Micro-harmony). - 2594. Nestrick, W.V. - 2595. Neuer, J. - 2596. Neuhauser, R. - 2597. Newark, L. - 2598. Newell, J.E. - 2599. Newman, R.S. (The tragedy of wit). - 2600. Newmark, L. (Readings in the transformational grammar of English). - 2601. Newmark, L. (Albanian reference grammar). - 2602. Newmeyer, F.J. - 2603. Newton, B. - 2604. Newton, R.P. - 2605. Newton, R.P. - 2606. Ney, J.W. - 2607. Ney, J.W. (Semantic structures for the syntax of complements and auxiliaries in English). - 2608. Nicholas, J.K. - 2609. Nichols, A.E. - 2610. Nichols, J.W. - 2611. Nicolich, R. (Triumph of spectacle). - 2612. Nicoloff, A. - 2613. Nida, E. - 2614. Nilsen, D.L.F. (Instrumental case). - 2615. Nilsen, D.L.F. (Meaning: a common ground of linguistics and literature). - 2616. Nilsen, D.L.F. (Toward a semantic specification of deep case). - 2617. Nilsen, D.L.F. (English adverbials). - 2618. Nilsson, N.A. (Hasek memorial volume). - 2619. Njock, H.M. Bot Ba - 2620. Nogle, L.E. (Method and theory in semantics). - 2621. Nolan, R. - 2622. Nooten, B.A. van - 2623. Norrell, L.N. (The Cuckold in restoration comedy). - 2624. Norton, B.G. - 2625. Norton, B.G. (Conventionalism, linguistic framework and ontology: a study in the metaontology of R. Carnap). - 2626. Norton, G.P. - 2627. Norwood, W.D. Jr. - 2628. Nosco, B.M. - 2629. Novotný, M. et al. - 2630. Nowakowska, M. - 2631. Nusser, P. - 2632. Nyirö, L. (Literature and its interpretation).
    - O
      2633. O’Bryan, M. (The history and dev. of verbal system of Early Middle Indic). - 2634. O’Connell, D. (The opposition: anti-symbolist criticism in the modern period). - 2635. O’Connor, K. (Pasternak’s ‘Sestra’). - 2636. O’Gorman, R. (Leo Spitzer). - 2637. O’Grady, G.N. - 2638. O’Leary, J.F. - 2639. O’Neal, C.R. - 2640. O’Neill, S.J. Jr. - 2641. O’Neill, W. (The evolution of the Germanic inflectional systems). - 2642. O’Neill, Y.V. - 2643. O’Rourke, J. (Toward a science of vocabulary devolopment). - 2644. Obolensky, A. (Gogol’). - 2645. Obolensky, A. (Leont’ev). - 2646. Obrecht, D.H. - 2647. Obuchowski, C.W. (Of Frenchmen and their wars). - 2648. Odabashian, P. (An onomastic study of ‘Doktor Živago’, a novel by B. Pasternak). - 2649. vacant. - 2650. Odom, P.B. - 2651. Ogibenin, B.L. - 2652. Ogulnick, K. (Allomorphy in linguistic theory). - 2653. Oh, C.-K. (Presuppositional grammar). - 2654. Ohnesorg, K. - 2655. Oinas, F.J. (Denis Sinor Festschrift). - 2656. Okby, M.M. - 2657. Oksaar, E. (Wort und Text). - 2658. Oldenburg, E.W. - 2659. Oléron, P. (Bulletin de psychologie). - 2660. Oléron, P. (Language and mental development). - 2661. Oliphant, R. - 2662. Oliverius, Z.F. - 2663. Oller, J. - 2664. Olley, F.B. - 2665. Ollier, M.-L. (Prolégomènes à une lecture du roman). - 2666. Olmstead, D.L. - 2667. Olsson, Y.B. - 2668. Olsson, Y.B. - 2669. Olteanu, P. - 2670. Omar, A.H. - 2671. Omar, M.K. - 2672. Ondráčková, J. - 2673. Onishi, M. (Japanese phonology). - 2674. Oomen, U. - 2675. Oransky, I.M. - 2676. Ornstein, J. - 2677. Ornstein, J. (Introduction to scientific Russian reading). - 2677bis. Ornstein, Jacob (Second steps in Russian). - 2678. Ortheguy, R.L. (The meaning of Spanish El, La and Lo). - 2679. Osborn, V.J. - 2680. Osgood, C.E. - 2681. Osgood, C.E. (Selected articles). - 2682. Osmond-Smith, D. - 2683. Osser, H. - 2684. Otanes, F.T. - 2685. Otlewski, E. - 2686. Ouden, B.D. den (Language and creativity: an interdisciplinary essay in Chomskyan humanism). - 2687. Oulanoff, H. - 2688. Oulanoff, H.(The prose fiction of Veniamin A. Kaverin: a study). - 2689. Overbeke, M. van (Modèles de l’interférence linguistique). - 2690. Overdulve, C.M.
    - P
      2691. Pachmuss, T. (Gippius’ works). - 2692. Packard, D.J. (A first course in the semantics and logic of English). - 2693. Padučeva, E.V. - 2694. Padučeva, E.V. (Bibliography). - 2695. Paessman, E. - 2696. Pagen, S.B. - 2697. Painter, C. - 2698. Pak, T.-Y. - 2699. Pak, T.-Y. - 2700. Palakornkul, A. (Thai pronouns). - 2701. Palmatier, R.A. - 2702. Palmer, R.E. Jr. - 2703. Palomo, D.J. (The syntax of revenge: a structuralist reading of English revenge drama). - 2704. Palter, L. - 2705. Palumbo, E. - 2706. Panel, H. - 2707. Panfilov, V.Z. - 2708. Panichas, G.A. - 2709. Paper, H. - 2710. Papp, F. - 2711. Parent, D.J. - 2712. Parent, D.J., and J. Bruce-Novoa (Entry into matter). - 2713. Paris, S.G. (Propositional logical thinking and comprehension of language connectives). - 2714. Parisi, D. - 2715. Park, L.G. - 2716. Park, P.V. - 2717. Park, T.-Z. (The development of syntax in the child with special reference to German). - 2718. Parker, D. (Enchiridion Militis Christiani). - 2719. Parker, G.J. - 2720. Parker-Rhodes, A.F. (Inferential semantics). - 2721. Parkinson, F.C. (The double truth theory in Chaucer’s ‘Troilus’). - 2722. Paroutaud, M. - 2723. Parret, H. - 2724. Parret, H. (History of linguistic thought and contemporary linguistics). - 2725. Parret, H. (Papers of De Saussure). - 2726. Parret, H. (ed.) (Discussing language, dialogues with...). - 2727. Partee, B.H. (Collected works). - 2728. Partee, M.H. - 2729. Passage, C.E. - 2730. Passon, R.H. - 2731. Paternost, J. - 2732. Patiño, C. - 2733. Pattanayak, D.P. - 2734. Patten, R.L. - 2735. Patterson, W., and H. Urrutibheity - 2736. Patterson, W. (A sequel to the lexical structure of Spanish). - 2737. Patton, H.B. - 2738. Pauliny, E. - 2739. Pearlman, D.D. - 2740. Peer, L.H. (Romanpoesie). - 2741. Peeters, G.J. (Everyman and Elkcerlye). - 2742. Peirce (Sound symbolism of Poe’s "The Raven"). - 2743. Pelc, J. - 2744. Penchoen, Th. - 2745. Peng, F.C.C. - 2746. Peng, F.C.C. - 2747. Peng, F.C.C. - 2748. Peng, F.C.C. (Chao anthology). - 2749. Penn, J.M. - 2750. Penot, D.M.P. - 2751. Penot, D.M.P. - 2752. Penzl, H. (Selected writings, I. Rauch, Ed.). - 2753. Penzl, H. - 2754. Percival, K. - 2755. Pereira, N.G.O. - 2756. Perek, Z. - 2757. Perkins, K. (Collection of papers on discourse analysis). - 2758. Perlmutter, D.M. (Collected works). - 2759. Perloff, M. - 2760. Permjakov, G.L. (From Proverb to Folktale). - 2761. Pernes, R. - 2762. Perreiah, A.R. - 2763. Perreiah, A.R. (Logica Parva (translation and intro. notes and essays)). - 2764. Perry, D.S. - 2765. Perry, M.F. - 2766. Perry, T.A. - 2767. Persson, A.V. - 2768. Persson, A.V. (Comic Characters in...). - 2769. Peškovskij, A.M. (Sovietica). - 2770. Peters, R.A. (The unseen woof: studies in Swinburne’s poetry). - 2771. Peters, R.A. - 2772. Peters, V. - 2773. Peterson, A.W. - 2774. Peterson, G.M. (Articles on phonetics). - 2775. Peterson, L.S. - 2776. Peterson, P.L. - 2777. Petöfi, J. (Grammatical aspects of text structures). - 2778. Petraček, K. - 2779. Petro, P. (Modern satire: four studies). - 2780. Petrovici, E. - 2781. Pfaff, L. (The devil in Thomas Mann’s ‘Doktor Faustus’). - 2782. Pfister, F.J. - 2783. Pheby, John (see: 313. Bierwisch, M. (Modern linguistics). - 2784. Pia, J.J. - 2785. Picchio, R. - 2786. Pierce, J.E. - 2787. Pierce, J.E. (Ling. anal. and Eng. gram.). - 2788. Pike, K.L. (Language in relation). - 2789. Pike, K. L. and E.V. (Live issues in descriptive linguistics). - 2790. Pilch, H. - 2791. Pilch, H. (Welsh grammar). - 2792. Pilleux, M. - 2793. Pillsbury, P.W. - 2794. Pilot, J. - 2795. Pinsker, S. - 2796. Pinsker, S. (The languages of Joseph Conrad). - 2797. Pinsky, R.N. - 2798. Piotrovskij, R.G. - 2799. Pipes, R. - 2800. Pisoni, D.B. (On the Nature of categorical perception of speech sounds). - 2801. Pitkin, H. - 2802. Pitkin, H. - 2803. Pitlick, M.L. - 2804. Pittock, M. - 2805. Plangg, G.A. - 2805bis. Plank, Dale L. - 2806. Plant, H.R. - 2807. Platt, J.F. - 2808. Plavilščikov, V.A. - 2809. Pletnev, R., and J.-Y. Le Guillou (Solženicyn). - 2810. Plötz, S. - 2811. Plotkin, V.Y. - 2812. Plummer, J.F. (Between march and april: form and tradition in the Middle English love lyric.). - 2813. Polčepcov, G.G. (A syntagmatic study of English word classes). - 2814. Polčepcov, G.G. - 2815. Polčepcov, G.G. (Constructional analysis of sentence structrure). - 2816. Polčepcov, G.G. (English sentence structure). - 2817. Polčepcov, G. (Selected essays on syntactic problems). - 2818. Poger, S.B. - 2819. Poinsatte, A.-M. (Nouvelles perspectives sur...). - 2820. Polański, K. - 2821. Politzer, R. (Language acquisition in two bilingual schools). - 2822. Polivanov, E.D. (Selected articles, I). - 2823. Polivanov, E.D. (Selected writings, II). - 2824. Pollio, H.R. - 2825. Polomé, E. (Translations (Guchman, M.M.)). - 2826. Polomé, E. (ed.) (Hill Festschrift). - 2827. Pomorska, K. - 2828. Pomorska, K. (Invariants and variables of Boris Pasternak). - 2829. Pomorski, S. - 2830. Pongweni, A.J.C. (The phonetics and phonology of the Karanga dialect of Shona). - 2831. Ponomareff, C.V. - 2832. Pope, E.N. (Questions and answers in English). - 2833. Popov, P. (Verbal forms in the Russian tales of the first third of the 17th century). - 2834. Poppe, A. (ed.) (A.V. Soloviev’s selected writings). - 2835. Poppe, N. (Wittfogel Festschrift). - 2836. Porten, B. - 2837. Porter, M.G. (The novels of Saul Bellow). - 2838. Pos, H.J. - 2839. Posada, R. - 2840. Posin, J.A. - 2841. Posner, R. - 2842. Postal, P.M. (Collection of articles). - 2843. Potter, R.A. - 2844. Pottier, B. (Études sémantiques). - 2845. Poulin, N.A. - 2846. Pound, G.M. - 2847. Poutsma, H. - 2848. Powell, G.E. - 2849. Powers, D.C. - 2850. Poynter, D.S. - 2851. Praninskas, J. - 2852. Prasad, P. - 2853. Pratt, T.W. - 2854. Prescott, E.K. - 2855. Preziosi, D. - 2856. Price, F.W. - 2857. Price, G.R. - 2858. Price, J.T. (Language and being in Wittgenstein’s Philosophical Investigation). - 2859. Price, W.O. (Evolution of realism in German poetry). - 2860. Prideaux, G.D. - 2861. Prier, R.A. - 2862. Prieto, J.L. - 2863. Prince, G. - 2864. Prince, G. (Narratology, the form and functioning of narrative). - 2865. Pritsak, O. - 2866. Prizel, Z. - 2867. Proctor, J.W. - 2868. Proffer, C. - 2869. Propp, V. (see: 422. Breymayer, R.). - 2870. Prucha, J. (Information sources in psycholinguistics). - 2871. Prucha, J. (Soviet psycholinguistics). - 2872. Prucha, J. (Soviet studies in language and behavior). - 2873. Prusek, J. - 2874. Prvulovič, Ž.R. - 2875. Pucci, P. - 2876. Pulcher, E.E.S. - 2877. Pulgram, E. (Introduction to the spectrography of speech). - 2878. Pulgram, E. (Revision of introduction to sound spectography by O’Malley). - 2879. Pulgram, E. - 2880. Purcell, Edward T. - 2881. Proctor, T. - 2882. Purdy, S.B. (Word and object in Henry James). - 2883. Puryear, J.R. Jr. - 2884. Puškarev, S.G. (Proischoždenie krestjanskoj pozemel’no-peredel’noj obščiny…). - 2885. Putzar, E.D. - 2886. Pütz, M. (The Story of identity: American fiction of the sixties). - 2887. Pütz, M. (The story of identity: American fiction of the sixties). - 2888. Pynsent, R.B.
    - Q
      2889. Quemada, B. (Bibliography). - 2890. Quiers, P.W. - 2891. Quillen, F.C.. - 2892. Quinting, G. - 2893. Quirk, R. - 2894. Quirk, R. (Linguistic acceptability). - 2895. Quirk, R. (Survey of English usage papers).
    - R
      2896. Radford, J.R. - 2897. Radley, P.D. - 2898. Raffel, B. - 2899. Ragusa, O. (Novelists and playwrights: essays in modern Italian literature). - 2900. Raizis, M.B. - 2901. Rallides, C. - 2902. Ramer, A.L.H. (Syntactic styles and universal aspects of language emergence). - 2903. Rankin, B.K. - 2904. Ransom, D.R. - 2905. Rarick, L. (Ten-syllable lines in English poetry). - 2906. Raskin, V.V. - 2907. Raskin, V. - 2908. Raskin, V. (200 problems in linguistics and mathematics). - 2909. Raskin, V. (A biannual report on contemporary Soviet linguistics). - 2910. Raskin, V. (K teorii jazykovych podsistem). - 2911. Rasmussen, D.F. (Poetry and truth: an inquiry into their relation). - 2912. Raspa, (The emotive image). - 2913. Raspa, A. (The emotive image). - 2914. Rathé, A.W. - 2915. Rauch, I. - 2916. Rauch, I. - 2917. Rauch, I. (Where does language borrowing end and genetic relationship begin). - 2918. Rault-Marčinova, M. - 2919. Raupach, M., and H.W. Dechert (eds.) (Temporal variables in speech). - 2920. Ray, H.H. - 2921. Ray, P.S. - 2922. Rayfield, J.R. - 2923. Raymond, M.B. - 2924. Razumovskij, A. - 2925. Rebing, G.O. - 2926. Reck, V.T. (Boris Pilnjak). - 2927. Redden, J.E. - 2928. Reddington, J.P. - 2929. Reddy, M. (Reference and metaphor). - 2930. Redfern, J.G. - 2931. Ree, J.J. (Some aspects of Korean syntax). - 2932. Reed, P.J. - 2933. Reed, R.L. (The function of folklore in selected English Gothic novels). - 2934. Rees, T.R. - 2935. Reeve, R.R. - 2936. Regalado, N.F. - 2937. Rehmus, E.E. (Babel rebuilt). - 2938. Reibel, D.A. - 2939. Reich, P. (A relational network model of language behavior). - 2940. Reichel, D.A. - 2941. Reichelt, H. - 2942. Reichling, A. (Het woord). - 2943. Reichman, O. (ed.) (Aufsätze und Vorträge zur Wortfeldtheorie von Jost Trier). - 2944. Reid, L. - 2945. Reiff, D.G. - 2946. Reiner, E. - 2947. Reinheimer-Pipeanu, S. (Les dérives parasynthétiques...). - 2948. Reiser, H. - 2949. Reklaitis, J.K. (Theory of analogical change: application to Lithuanian). - 2950. Renaldi, T.W. (Analysing Los de Abajo...). - 2951. Rench, C.R. - 2952. Rensch, K.H.M. (Nordkalabrischer Sprachatlas anhand der Parabel vom verlorenen Sohn). - 2953. Resch, Y. - 2954. Resnick, M. - 2955. Reuter, F. (The structure of the Old English ‘Exodus’). - 2956. Revutsky, V. - 2957. Revzin, I.I. - 2958. Revzin, I.I. (Modeli jazyka). - 2959. Revzin, I.I. (Osnovy obščego i mašinnogo perevoda). - 2960. Revzin, I.I. (Strukturelle Grammatik des Deutschen). - 2961. Revzin, I.I. (The origin of language). - 2962. Revzina, O. - 2963. Reynolds, A.L. - 2964. Reynolds, J.D. - 2965. Rhamm, M. - 2966. Rice, L.M. (Mediaeval German Benedictine and Franciscan Homiletic style IX- XIV Centuries). - 2967. Rice, P.A.P. - 2968. Richards, H.J. - 2969. Richardson, J. - 2970. Richman, S.H. - 2971. Richmond, H.M. - 2972. Richter, M. (Phon. system of Penn. Germ.). - 2973. Ricks, D.M. - 2974. Rickwood, T. - 2975. Rieber, R.W. (A psycholinguistic investigation of stuttering and cluttering). - 2976. Ries, J.S. - 2977. vacant. - 2978. Riffaterre, M. - 2979. Riffaterre, M. (L’engendrement du texte). - 2980. Rigault, A. (Phonetic series). - 2981. Rigault, A. (ed.) (Proceedings of phonetics congress). - 2982. Riggs, E.P. - 2983. Rigsby, B.J. - 2984. Ring, J.W. (Peirce’s contribution to a logic of discovery). - 2985. Ritchie, W.C. - 2986. Rivero, M.-L. - 2987. Robbins, F.E. - 2988. Roberts, A.H. - 2989. Roberts, E.B. - 2990. Roberts, J.W. - 2991. Roberts, S.E. - 2992. Robertson, D.C. - 2993. Robertson, J. (Transitions and perspective in the narrative fiction of Marcel Proust). - 2994. Robinson, D.F. - 2995. Robinson, F. M. (The comedy of language). - 2996. Robinson, L.W. (A Mandarin grammar sketch in the transformational model). - 2997. Robinson, P. - 2998. Rochet, B. (The formation and the evolution of the French nasal vowels...). - 2999. Rochette-Ozzelo, Y. (French exclamatory sentences). - 3000. Rocklage, M.N. - 3001. Rockwood, H.M. (A syntactic analysis of selected Middle High German prose as a basis). - 3002. Rogers, D.E. - 3003. Rogers, T.F. - 3004. Rogger, H. - 3005. Rohrberger, M. - 3006. Rojas, N. (On the syntactic structures of derivational suffixation in French). - 3007. Roldán, M. de las Mercedes - 3008. Rollin, B.E., and J. Rieux (Grammaire générale et raisonnée). - 3009. Rollins, P.C. - 3010. Romeo, L. - 3011. Romportl, M. (Studies in phonetics). - 3012. Ronat, M. - 3013. Ronen, O. - 3014. Römer, R.G. (Papiamentu). - 3015. Rozencvejg, V.Ju (see also: 3058-3059. Rozencvejg, V.Ju.). - 3016. Rozencvejg, V.Ju. (Dictionary project) (see also: 3058-3059. Rozencvejg, V.Ju). - 3017. Rozencvejg, V.Ju. (Soviet studies in morphology and formal linguistics) (see also: 3058-3059. Rozencvejg, V.Ju.). - 3018. Rose, C.B. (Jakobson’s method applied to free verse: an analysis of Pound’s "usura canto"). - 3019. Rosén, H.B. - 3020. Rosén, H.B. - 3021. Rosén, H.B. (Gothic language samples). - 3022. Rosen, N. - 3023. Rosen, R. - 3024. Rosen, R.S. - 3025. Rosenberg, B.A. - 3026. Rosenberg, S.N. - 3027. Rosenberg, S. (Semantic intergration: a psycholinguistic approach). - 3028. Rosenfeld, N. - 3029. Rosenfeld, S. - 3030. Rosenfield, L.W. - 3031. Rosenthal, B. - 3032. Rosetti, A. - 3033. Rosetti, A. - 3034. Rosetti, A. (Brève histoire de la langue roumaine). - 3035. Rosier, J. (Meritt Festschrift). - 3036. Ross, A.S.C. (Commentary on the Anglo-Saxon Durham ritual). - 3037. Ross, A.S.C. (Edition of Aelfric’s Latin grammar). - 3038. Ross, A.S.C. (Indoeuropean numerals). - 3039. Ross, A.S.C. (ed.) (Indoeuropean numerals). - 3040. Ross, J.M. - 3041. Ross, J.R. - 3042. Ross, J.R. (English word stress and helping verbs). - 3043. Rossi-Landi, F. (Linguistics and economics). - 3044. Rossi, V. - 3045. Rosslyn, W. (Religious aspects of the work of Anna Akhmatova). - 3046. Rossman, V.R. (Perspectives of Irony in Medieval French Literature). - 3047. Rostvig, M.-S. (Fair forms: essays in Eng. lit.). - 3048. Rot (Problems of Hungarian-East-Slavic linguistic contacts). - 3049. Rothemberg, M. - 3050. Rothrock, I.-S. - 3051. Rouben, C. (Bussy-Rabutin correspondance). - 3052. Roudil, J. (Actes del II Colloqui International sobre el Catala). - 3053. Roudil, J. (La tradition manuscrite de Cuenca: essais de linguistique textuelle). - 3054. Roudil, J., and L. - 3055. Rountree, M.M. - 3056. Rousseau, C. J. - 3057. Roza, R. - 3058. Rozencvejg, V.Ju. (Linguistic interference and convergent change). - 3059. Rozencvejg, V.Ju. (Anthology: languages in contact). - 3060. Roždestvenskij, Ju.V. (Tipologija slova). - 3061. Rubin, J. - 3062. Rubulis, A. - 3063. Rudy, P. - 3064. Ruhlen, M. (Romanian Phonology). - 3065. Ruiz, M.B. - 3066. Runzo, J.P. (Aspects of English criticism of the novel, 1830-1850). - 3067. Rus, V. - 3068. Rusiecki, J. - 3069. Russell, W.M. - 3070. Russell, W.M. (Poetics analysis and literary history). - 3071. Rutherford, P.R. - 3072. Ruthrof, H.G. (Construction of meaning seminar). - 3073. Rutten, P.M. van (Saint-John Perse). - 3074. Rutten, P.M. van - 3075. Rutten, P.M. van (Concordances of word frequency). - 3076. Ruwet, N. - 3077. Ružička, R. - 3078. Ryder, S.A. - 3079. Ryding, W.W.
    - S
      3080. Saada, L. - 3081. Saalmann, D. - 3082. Šachmatov, A.A. - 3083. Šachmatov, A.A. (Historical grammar). - 3084. Šachmatov, A.A. (Russian historical dialect.). - 3085. Sadikov, P.A. - 3086. Sadnik, L., and R. Aitzetmüller (Handwörterbuch zu den altkirchenslavischen Texten.). - 3087. Safarewicz, J. - 3088. Saha, P.K. - 3089. Saíz, P. (The persona in medieval love lyric). - 3090. Sakbani, A. - 3091. Sala, M. - 3092. Sala, M. - 3093. Salm, P. - 3094. Salmond, A, - 3095. Salomon, L.B. - 3096. Saltarelli, M. - 3097. Saltarelli, M. - 3098. Saltarelli, M., and D. Wanner (eds.). - 3099. Salter, F.R. (Numerical duality and grammatical number in Old Russian). - 3100. Salus, P.H. - 3101. Salzmann, Z. - 3102. Samarin, W.J. - 3103. Sambor, J. (Słowa i liczby: Zagadnienia językoznawstwa statystycznego). - 3104. Samilov, M. - 3105. Sampson, G. - 3106. Sampson, G.P. - 3107. Sampson, H.G. - 3108. Samuelsdorf, P. - 3109. San Jose, C. (In the mind and onto the Paper.). - 3110. Sanborn, D.A. - 3111. Sanches, M. - 3112. Sanders, C. - 3113. Sanders, G.A. - 3114. Sanders, G.A. (Domain...). - 3115. Sanders, G.A. (On the equational nature of G.). - 3116. Sanders, R.E. - 3117. Sangster, R.B. (Journal, History of Linguistica). - 3118. Sangster, R.B. (Language as a system of signs). - 3119. Sankoff, D. - 3120. Sannikov, V.Z. - 3121. Sara, S.I. - 3122. Saradzenidze, T.S. - 3123. Sargent, S.H. - 3124. Sarot, R.-A. (Les effects sociosémantiques de la structure sociale). - 3125. Sastri, M.I. - 3126. Satta, L. - 3127. Sattler, E.E. - 3128. Šaumjan, S.K. - 3129. Šaumjan, S.K (Theoretical phonology). - 3130. Šaumjan, S.K. (Structural linguistics). - 3131. Šaumjan, S.K. (A semantic theory of natural languages). - 3132. Šaumjan, S.K. (ed.) (Structural word formation dictionary). - 3133. Saunders, G. (The use and function of modal particles in Modern German). - 3134. Saussure, F. de - 3135. Savić, P. (ed.) (Collection on A. Belić). - 3136. Sayre, R.W. (Solitude in society: a sociological study in French literature). - 3137. Scaglione, A.D. - 3138. Scanlan, M. (William Faulkner and the search for lost time). - 3139. Scatton, E. - 3140. Ščerba, L.V. (Sovietica). - 3141. Schäfer, J. - 3142. Schadlich, H.J. - 3143. Schaefer, J. - 3144. Schaerlaekens, A.M. (Contribution to the study of child language). - 3145. Scheindlin, R.P. - 3146. Schell, E.T. - 3147. Schenkel, W. - 3148. Schenker, A.M. - 3149. Schenker, A.M. - 3150. Scherer-Verski, O. - 3151. Schick, E.B. - 3152. Schindler, M.S. - 3153. Schlant, E. - 3154. Schleier, I.E.H. (Das Funktionssystem der Präpostitionalkonstruktion). - 3155. Schlesinger, I.M. - 3156. Schmalstieg, W.R. - 3157. Schmalstieg, W.R. - 3158. Schmidt, F. (Symbolische Syntax). - 3159. Schmidt, N.J. - 3160. Schmidt-Radefeldt, J. - 3161. Schmidt, S., and P. Hartmann (Theory and philosophy of language). - 3162. Schmidt, T. - 3163. Schmidtberger, L.F. - 3164. Schimizzi, J.A.J. (Synonymy among Russian primary prepositions). - 3165. Schneider, G. - 3166. Schnitzer, M.L. - 3167. Schoff, G. - 3168. Schogt, H. - 3169. Scholes, R.J. - 3170. Scholes, R.J. - 3171. Scholler, H. (ed.) (Lexicography and dialectology). - 3172. Scholz, B.F. (A phenomenological interpretation of organic metaphors...). - 3173. Scholz, F. - 3174. Schonhorn, M. - 3175. Schooneveld, C.H. van (Contemp. standard Russian). - 3176. Schooneveld, C.H. van (The Russian preposition). - 3177. Schorrig, E.W. - 3178. Schote, J. - 3179. Schramm, G.M. - 3180. Schramm, L.J. (The apotheosis of solitude: the Textes pour rien of Samuel Beckett). - 3181. Schramm, M.S. - 3182. Schroten, J. - 3183. Schubert, M. - 3184. Schueler, H.J. - 3185. Schuhmacher, W.W. - 3186. Schuhmacher, W.W. - 3187. Schuhmacher, W.W. (Friedrich Engels als Sprachwissenschaftler). - 3188. Schuhmacher, W.W. (On the linguistic aspect of Thor Heyerdahl’s theory). - 3189. Schulte, R.O. - 3190. Schultz, E. (Gotisches Glossar). - 3191. Schulz, H.J. - 3192. Schuman, L.O. (Semitic etymology and historical linguistics). - 3193. Schupbach, R.D. (Russian substantival derivation). - 3194. Schurer, E. - 3195. Schutz, A.J. - 3196. Schveiger, P. (Speech pathology). - 3197. Schwane, J.G. (The Latin preposition in with personal object). - 3198. Schwartz, B. - 3199. Schwartz, R.A. - 3200. Sciarone, A.G. - 3201. Sciarone, A.G. - 3202. Scott, Robert I. - 3203. Scott, W.G. (A systematization and critical analysis). - 3204. Scott, W.C. - 3205. Scovel, T. (A grammar of time in Thai). - 3206. Scriabine, H. - 3207. Scruggs, C.W. - 3208. Ščur, G.S. - 3209. Ščur, G.S. (Selected writings). - 3210. Ščur, G.S. (Teorija polja v lingvistike). - 3211. Seaman, P.D. - 3212. Searle, L.F. - 3213. Sebeok, T.A. - 3214. Sebeok, T.A.. - 3215. Sebeok, T.A. (Semiotics and all other). - 3216. Sebeok, T.A. (Essays in Cheremis verb. art). - 3217. Sebeok, T.A. (Native languages of the Americas). - 3218. Sebeok, T.A. (Perspectives in zoosemiotics). - 3219. Sebeok, T.A. (Reprint of Approaches to semiotics). - 3220. Sebüktekin, H.I. - 3221. Sečkarev, V. - 3222. Secrist, R.H. Jr. - 3223. Seduro, V. - 3224. Seduro, V. (Dostoevsky and world theatre). - 3225. Seebold, E. - 3226. Seely, K.G. - 3227. Seiden, W. - 3228. Seigel, A.H. - 3229. Seiler, H. - 3230. Seiler, H. - 3231. Selegen, G. (The World as I see it ( A. Chekhov and literature of sensations)). - 3232. Sel’vinskij, I. - 3233. Seright, O.D. - 3234. Servodidio d’Ambrosio, M. - 3235. Sessions, W.A. - 3236. Ševoroškin, V. - 3237. Seward, R. - 3238. Sexton, R.J. - 3239. Seyffert, P. - 3240. Shands, H. 3240bis. Shane, A.M. - 3241. Shannon, A. - 3242. Shapiro, A. - 3243. Shapiro, B.C. (A pollen of Edeas: a comparative study of James Joyce and William Faulkner). - 3244. Shapiro, M. - 3245. Shapiro, M. (Aspects...). - 3246. Shapiro, M. (Journey to the metonymic pole: the structure of Pushkin’s "Little tragedies"). - 3247. Shapiro, M. (Towards...). - 3248. Sharazenidze, T. (Theoretical problems in modern linguistics). - 3249. Sharma, M.L. - 3250. Sharma, R.N. - 3251. Sharpless, E. (Children’s acquisition of personal pronouns). - 3252. Sheaffer, M.P.A. - 3253. Shedd, G.M. - 3254. Sheldahl, T.K. - 3255. Sheldahl, T.K. - 3256. Sheldon, R.R. - 3257. Shell, O.A. - 3258. Shani, A.R.M. (A linguistic analysis of tense and time in Arabic). - 3259. Shepler, F.J. - 3260. Sheppard, V. - 3261. Sherwood, R.J. (Russian formalist school project). - 3262. Sherzer, Joel - 3263. Shevelov, G.Y. (Ukrainian; Ševčenko). - 3264. Shibles, W.A. - 3265. Shinall, S.L. - 3266. Shmeifsky, M. - 3267. Shook, M.L. - 3268. Shopen, T. - 3269. Shores, D.L. - 3270. Shoup, J.E. (Articles on phonetics). - 3271. Shoup, J.E. - 3272. Shugar, G.W. (Language acquisition within the developing behaviour stream). - 3273. Shukla, S. (Bhojpuri syntax). - 3274. Shulman, R. - 3275. Shuter, W.F. - 3276. Siebenschuh, W. (Form and purpose in Boswell’s …). - 3277. Siebert, D.T. Jr. (Samuel Johnson and the style of satire). - 3278. Siedlecki - 3279. Siekmann, R.C.R. (Struktuur en terminologie van het voetbalspel). - 3280. Silver, B.L. (Critical review of Anglo-Saxon metrics). - 3281. Silver, S.K. - 3282. Silverman, E.B. - 3283. Simanis, L.P. - 3284. Simeon, G.J. - 3285. Simmons, J.C. - 3286. Simons, J.D. - 3287. Simonton, T.E. - 3288. Sinclair, C. - 3289. Singh, R. - 3290. Singh, R. (The notion sentence type). - 3291. Singh, S. - 3292. Sinor, D. (ed.) (Raun Festschrift). - 3293. Skwarcsyńska, S. (Papers from conf. on Slavic poetics and stylistics, Warsaw). - 3294. Skwarcsyńska, S. (ed.) (Polish contributions to the Warsaw congress). - 3295. Skendi, S. (Balkan cultural studies). - 3296. Skinner, J.L. - 3297. Skousen, R. (Substantive evidence for morphological and phonetic regularities...). - 3298. Skulicz, M.V. - 3299. Skulsky, H. (Doubt and vision: the defeat of meaning in Donne and Crashaw). - 3300. Slagle, U.V. - 3301. Slama-Cazacu, T. (Communication in the process of working). - 3302. Slama-Cazacu, T. (Dialogul La Copii). - 3303. Slama-Cazacu, T. (Introduction into psycholinguistics). - 3304. Slama-Cazacu, T. (Langage et context). - 3305. Slama-Cazacu, T. (Mouton). - 3306. Slater, J.G. - 3307. Sljusareva, N.A. (Sovietica). - 3308. Smerud, W.B. - 3309. Smirnickij, A.I. (Collected articles). - 3310. Smirnickij, A.I. (Sovietica). - 3311. Smith, B.H. - 3312. Smith, E.M. (Trager Festschrift). - 3313. Smith, J.W. (A history of the dictionary of English usage to 1900). - 3314. Smith, M.R. (Classical Arabic and colloquial Cairene: etc.). - 3315. Smith, P.T. - 3316. Smith, R. - 3317. Smith, R.S. - 3318. Smith, S.B. (Meaning and negation). - 3319. Smith, W.F. - 3320. Smyrniw, W. (Character types in Ivan Turgenev’s early works). - 3321. Snow, J. - 3322. Snyder, L. - 3323. Sobolevskij, A.I. - 3324. Solle, R. (Morphographisch-strukturelle Ableitungshierarchie eines Modell-Universums...). - 3325. Solomon, P.H. (Life after birth: imagery in Samuel Beckett’s Trilogy). - 3326. Somers, H. H. - 3327. Sommer, G.D. - 3328. Sommerfelt, A. - 3329. Söderbergh, R. (Project child language). - 3330. Söderbergh, R. (Reading in early childhood). - 3331. Sötèr, I. - 3332. Sorelle, Z.R. - 3333. Sorokin, O.G. - 3334. Sorrells, M.S. (Black dialect: current linguistic studies and black American novels). - 3335. Sotiropoulos, D. - 3336. Sotiropoulos, D. (Readings in Modern Greek diglossia). - 3337. Součková, M. - 3338. Soudakoff, S., and F. Oinas - 3339. Soudek, L. - 3340. Soules, E.H. - 3341. Sousa, A. de - 3342. Southworth, F.C. - 3343. Souza, R. de - 3344. Sova, L.Z. (Problems in operational grammar). - 3345. Sova, L.Z. (Analytical linguistics). - 3346. Spa, J.J. (Wagenia). - 3347. Spangenberg, K. - 3348. Spasov, D. - 3349. Spatz, J. - 3350. Spear, R.L. - 3351. Spears, R.A. - 3352. Spector, A. - 3353. Spencer, A.J. - 3354. Spencer, S. (Archetonic novel). - 3355. Spiegler, M. - 3356. Spinka, M. - 3357. Spitzbart - 3358. Spolsky, B. - 3359. Spreen, O. - 3360. Spring, G.K. - 3361. Springer, G.P. - 3362. Sroka, K. - 3363. Stacy, R.H. - 3364. Stade, G. - 3365. Stahl, F.A. - 3366. Stahl, F.A. - 3367. Stahlberger, L.L. - 3368. Staines, D. (Tennyson’s Camelot: a study of Tennyson’s Arthurian world and it’s medieval sources). - 3369. Staines, D. (Tennyson’s Camelot: the idylls of the king and its dedieval sources.). - 3370. Stalker, D.F. (Deep structure). - 3371. Stalker, J.C. (The stylistic and interpretative functions of relative clauses in ….). - 3372. Stanford, R.B. - 3373. Stanford, R. - 3374. Stankiewicz, E. (Russian substantives). - 3375. Stankiewicz, E. (Cultural history of the Slavs...). - 3376. Stankiewicz, E. (Dictionary of Slavic accents). - 3377. Stankiewicz, E. (Selected writings, vol. I: Synchronic and diachronic phonology). - 3378. Stankiewicz, E. (Selected writings, vol. II: Morphophonemics). - 3379. Stankiewicz, E. (Selected writings, col. III: Morphology). - 3380. Stankiewicz, E., and D. Worth (Bibl. of Slav. ling.). - 3381. Stanton, D.C. (The well-wrought man: a comparative of the "Honnête Homme" and the dandy). - 3382. Stark, B.R. - 3382bis. Starling, Betty. - 3383. Starobinski, J. - 3384. Starobinski, J. (Manuscripts F. de Saussure). - 3385. Starosta, S. - 3386. Stavan, H.A. - 3387. Stavrou, C. - 3388. Steele, E. (Henry Arthur Jones). - 3389. Stefano, J.S. De (Applied linguistics for teachers). - 3390. Steinberg, A.N. (Reference and description). - 3391. Steinberg, D.D. - 3392. Steinberg, D.D. - 3393. Steiner, P. - 3394. Steiner, P., and W. (Mukařovský). - 3395. Steiner, R.J. - 3396. Steiner, W., and P. (S. Karcevskij: Selected articles). - 3397. Steinhauer, H. (Čakavian studies). - 3398. Steinitz, W. (Collected works). - 3399. Steinke, G. - 3400. Steinke, J.E. (Life and work of Hugo Ball). - 3401. Stemmer, N. - 3402. Stenbock-Fermor, E. (Architecture in ‘Anna Karenina’). - 3403. Stepanenko, M. - 3404. Stephan, P. - 3405. Sterne, L. - 3406. Sterrenburg, L. (Indiana University English lecture series: beyond aestheticism). - 3407. Stevens, A.M. - 3408. Stevick, R.D. - 3409. Stevick, R.D. - 3410. Steward, W.R. - 3411. Stewart, G.M. - 3412. Ste